You are a minister of God.
Yes, Prophet.
Don't give up.
God loves you, please.
I know you are facing so much, what you are facing is not even persecution;
it's destruction and has given you a name that you use evil powers.
Don't give up because you are in between to leave the ministry and rest.
Yes, Prophet.
Between to leave the ministry...
You have branches in many places but you are in between saying,
"I want to handover for somebody to continue, I want to leave the ministry."
Yes, Prophet.
You think you have gotten to the cross-roads, left for you, this is the way you see the whole thing.
Don't give up, sir.
Yes, Prophet.
What is the cause of these thoughts?
The cause of the thoughts is that I have ministers under me.
In December, three ministers fell into the river when they were baptising converts and they died.
In your ministry?
In my ministry and then the people said that I bewitched those ministers.
That you are the one who killed them, that you used evil powers?
Yes.
This man is a man of God, the trouble just came like that.
He is not using evil powers.
It's all right.
While the prayer was going on, I saw someone across -
"This man wants to leave the ministry, the ministry you have been right from young age and you have been
the minister of God, God has planted the ministry into many places."
They say they will kill me.
They said they would kill you?
Yes, Prophet.
OK, it's all right.
We will discuss that.
No problem.
I'm seeing you as a minister of God, nobody can kill you.
There is no trace of evil in you.
They went from baptism and the three of them fell inside the river and died.
Three ministers of God and they said you are a wizard.
Are you the wife?
Yes, sir, I'm the wife.
I praise God for delivering him.
I am Archbishop Andrew Ndubano from Botswana.
I belong to the St. John's Apostolic Faith Mission of Botswana.
The lady standing next to me is my wife.
What is your name?
I'm a Lady Archbishop of St. John's Apostolic Faith Mission of Botswana.
You are welcome in Jesus' name.
Can you tell us what was the message of prophecy given to you today by Prophet T.B. Joshua?
I am in Lagos, Nigeria at the SCOAN.
Today is my day.
I have been very much amazed.
The prophet has been going around, picking out people and prophesying to them.
But to my greatest dismay, he came to me, held my hand and said, "You are a man of God,
you have a ministry. Now you are facing destruction
whom they labelled that you have killed the three ministers."
You are a minister of God.
Yes, Prophet.
Don't give up.
God loves you, please.
I know you are facing so much, what you are facing is not even persecution;
it's a destruction and that has given you a name that you used evil powers.
"I am declaring that you are innocent and there is nothing to bother you, or to worry you
as you have the intention of leaving the church."
Don't give up because you are in between to leave the ministry and rest.
Yes, Prophet.
This man is a man of God, the trouble just came like that.
He is not using evil powers.
It's all right.
What happened is that one of the branches with its own ministers decided to go and baptize
people on that particular date.
I was not informed of the day of the baptism; I only got a shock when I was phoned that I had bewitched
the three ministers that had drowned.
I had no knowledge of what could have happened.
The prophecy is excellent.
We thank God.
Finally, what decision are you going to take now after this prophecy?
After the prophecy, that the prophet proved beyond reasonable doubt and proving that I'm innocent...
He prophesied that I wanted to abandon my church
and now I'm not going to abandon the ministry as I started it.
I am now strengthened by the prophecy of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I am going to stay in the church until I die.
Hallelujah!
We thank you so much for this wonderful confirmation of the prophecy.
We give thanks to God for your life and for your ministry and we pray that God will give you that grace
to make His word the standard for your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Glory be to Jesus.